Finding Aid for John and Leni Sinclair Papers 1957-2003
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The Sinclair papers provide a rich and unique source for the study of America's radical movement in the nineteen sixties and seventies. Beginning with a remarkable series of correspondence that includes letters from Abbie Hoffman, Allen Ginsberg, Timothy Leary, and Jerry Rubin, and continuing on through extensive subject files, the collection details the cultural, political and business activities of a man whose energy and charisma made him a local and national leader of the counterculture. In addition, the collection documents the support and creativity of his wife and partner, who as writer, photographer and publicist helped to showcase the lifestyle which he symbolized.
Throughout the 1980s and 1990s, John Sinclair added to his papers with materials relating to his career as a writer and performer. In the winter of 2000, he donated a second large accession relating mainly to the period since leaving Detroit for New Orleans.
The Sinclair collection has been divided into four subgroups: Textual Files, Printed Material, Sound Recordings, and Visual Material.
Subjects - Textual Materials:
Sinclair, John, 1941-; Human Rights Party (Ann Arbor, Mich.); Drug abuse.; Rock music.; Musicians--Michigan.; Poetry.; United States--Politics and government--1963-1969.; Michigan--Politics and government--1961-1970.; United States--Politics and government--1974-1977.; United States--Politics and government--1969-1974.; Michigan--Politics and government--1971-1980.; Radicalism--Michigan.; Prisons--Michigan.; Marijuana.; Ann Arbor Blues and Jazz Festival.; First Zenta Church (Ann Arbor, Mich.); Ann Arbor Sun.; Artists' Workshop (Detroit, Mich.); MC5 (Musical group); Michigan Committee for Prisoner's Rights.; Rainbow Energies, Inc.; Rainbow Multi-Media Corporation.; Rainbow Peoples Party (Ann Arbor, Mich.); Strata Corporation.; Trans-Love Energies Unlimited.; UP (Musical group); White Panther Party.; Youth International Party.; Wayne State University. Artists Society.; Ann Arbor Tribal Council.; Tribal Council (Detroit, Mich.); Ann Arbor Blues Festival.
Contributors - Textual Materials:
Sinclair, Leni, 1940-; Bursley, Gilbert E.; Davis, Rennie.; Ginsberg, Allen, 1926-; Grimshaw, Gary.; Hart, Philip A. (Philip Aloysius), 1912-1976.; Hoffman, Abbie.; Leary, Timothy, 1920-1996.; Perret, Christopher, 1935-1965.; Plamondon, Pun.; Rubin, Jerry.; Vaughn, Jackie.
Subjects - Visual Material:
Abandoned buildings.; Activists.; Afro-Americans--Michigan.; Ann Arbor Art Fairs (Ann Arbor, Mich.); Ann Arbor (Mich.)--Business enterprises.; Ann Arbor (Mich.)--Social life and customs.; Ann Arbor (Mich.)--Politics and government.; Artists' Workshop (Detroit, Mich.); Baseball.; Ann Arbor Blues and Jazz Festival.; Blues music.; Busing (School integration); Cartoons.; Demonstrations.; Detroit (Mich.)--Buildings, structures, etc.; Detroit (Mich.)--Social life and customs.; Detroit Tigers (Baseball team); Drug abuse.; Hash Bash (Ann Arbor, Mich.); Abandoned buildings.; Activists.; Afro-Americans--Michigan.; Ann Arbor Art Fairs (Ann Arbor, Mich.); Ann Arbor (Mich.)--Business enterprises.; Ann Arbor (Mich.)--Social life and customs.; Ann Arbor (Mich.)--Politics and government.; Artists' Workshop (Detroit, Mich.); Baseball.; Ann Arbor Blues and Jazz Festival.; Blues music.; Busing (School integration); Cartoons.; Demonstrations.; Detroit (Mich.)--Buildings, structures, etc.; Detroit (Mich.)--Social life and customs.; Detroit Tigers (Baseball team); Drug abuse.; Hash Bash (Ann Arbor, Mich.); Human Rights Party (Ann Arbor, Mich.); Jazz music.; Manners and customs--1961-1970.; Manners and customs--1971-1980.; Marijuana.; Music--Michigan--Detroit.; Music--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Music festivals--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Musicians--Michigan--Detroit.; Musicians--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Newspaper industry.; Parades and processions.; Poets.; Radicalism--Michigan.; Rock music.
Contributors - Visual Materials:
Sinclair, John, 1941-; Sinclair, Leni, 1940-; Ann Arbor Blues Festival.; Ann Arbor Sun.; Eckert, Bob.; Grimshaw, Gary.; Johnson, David.; Marks, Michael.; Ross, Linda.; Sinclair, Leni, 1940-; Sun (Detroit, Mich.: 1967); Unangst, Joel.; Weinberg, Barbara, 1950-; Wiatrak, Ken.
Subjects - Sound Recordings:
Ann Arbor (Mich.). Common Council.; Ann Arbor (Mich.)--Politics and government.; Ann Arbor (Mich.)--Social conditions.; Ann Arbor Blues and Jazz Festival.; Communal living--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Disc jockeys.; Hippies--Michigan--Ann Arbor--Social life and customs.; Human Rights Party (Ann Arbor, Mich.); Jazz musicians.; Lightnin (Rock music group); MC5 (Musical group); Marijuana.; Michigan--Politics and government--1961-1970.; Michigan--Politics and government--1971-1980.; Plamondon, Pun--Trials, litigation, etc.; Poetry.; Popular music radio stations.; Prisons--Michigan.; Radicalism--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Radicals--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Radio broadcasting--Michigan.; Rainbow Peoples Party (Ann Arbor, Mich.); Riots--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Rock music--1961-1970.; Rock musicians.; Sinclair, John, 1941--Trials, litigation, etc.; Sinclair, Leni, 1940-; Trials (Narcotic laws)--Michigan--Wayne County.; Trials (Narcotic laws)--Michigan--Wexford County.; Ann Arbor Tribal Council.; University of Michigan--Students--Political activity.; UP (Musical group); White Panther Party.; Demonstrations--Michigan--Ann Arbor.
Contributors: Sound Recordings:
Ann Arbor Blues Festival.; Lightnin (Rock music group); Plamondon, Genie.; Plamondon, Pun.; Rainbow Multi-Media Corporation.; Sinclair, Leni, 1940-; Strata Corporation.; Trans-Love Energies Unlimited.
Genre/Form:
Photographs.; Photonegatives.; Posters.; Sound recordings.
- Textual Records
  - Biographical
    - Clippings, resumes, press releases(4 folders), 4 folders (Box 1)
    - Family history (Box 1)
    - Book catalog (Box 1)
    - Rolling Stone Article Index (Box 1)
  - Correspondence
    The Correspondence series has been arranged chronologically. For the period 1969-1971, the correspondence was sorted down to the day; for the years before and after, it was sorted down to the month only. Correspondence from the years 1978 to 1999 was sorted to the year. The series also includes a "name file" which was maintained by Sinclair during the 1980s and 1990s. The researcher interested in examining Sinclair's correspondence with a particular individual is advised to check both the name file and the chronological correspondence; correspondents with entries in the name file may also appear in the chronological correspondence. Whenever possible, correspondence concerned with specific subjects or relating to the operations of one of the Sinclair organizations has been left with the appropriate subject file or organizational records. Appended to this finding aid is a selective index to some of the correspondents within the collection.
    - Undated, 1962-April 1966, 41 folders (Box 1)
    - May 1966-September 1969, 40 folders (Box 2)
    - October 1969-May 1970, 28 folders (Box 3)
    - June 1970-1971, undated, 29 folders (Box 4)
    - January 1971-August 1971, 36 folders (Box 5)
    - September 1971-December 1987, 42 folders (Box 6)
    - 1988-1999, 11 folders (Box 45)
    - Correspondence Name file
      - Adler, Bill 1980s (Box 45)
      - Bach, Frank 1975-1995 (Box 45)
      - Browell, Nick 1996 (Box 45)
      - Buri, Tom 1995-1996 (Box 45)
      - Duncan, Harry 1980s (Box 45)
      - Dumont, Frank 1989 (Box 45)
      - Edmonds, Ben 1988 (Box 45)
      - Gulyas, Ron ("Big Red") 1996-1997 (Box 45)
      - Goldman, Albert 1983-1984 (Box 45)
      - Howrilla, Paul 1982 (Box 45)
      - Hutton, Bill 1970s (scattered dates) (Box 45)
      - Jones, Linda 1988 (Box 45)
      - Kelley, Ken 1970s-1980s (scattered dates), 2 folders (Box 45)
      - Kramer, Wayne 1997 (Box 45)
      - Larson, Goat 1996 (Box 45)
      - Lichter, Paul 1980s (scattered dates) (Box 45)
      - Lubbell, David 1974-1977 (Box 45)
      - McGlyn, Jim 1996 (Box 45)
      - Metcalf, Johnny, no dates (Box 45)
      - Michel, Ed 1982 (Box 45)
      - Normille, Henry 1979 (Box 45)
      - Oschenschlager, Nancy 1977-1983 (Box 45)
      - Papini, Piedro 1997 (Box 45)
      - Phelan, Tim 1988 (Box 45)
      - Pinkston, Richard 1982 (Box 45)
      - Plamondon, Larry ("Pun") 1980s-1990s (scattered dates) (Box 45)
      - Rudnick, Bob ("Righteous Rudnick") 1980s-1990s (scattered dates) (Box 45)
      - Sanders, Ed 1970s-1990s (scattered dates) (Box 45)
      - Semark, Jim 1987-1989 (Box 45)
      - Seymour, Tony, 1970s (Box 45)
      - Sherman, Dorothy 1982-1988 (scattered dates) (Box 45)
      - Simmons, Michael 1996-1997 (Box 7)
      - Sinclair, Celia 1980s-1990s (scattered dates) (Box 7)
      - Sinclair, David 1980s-1990s (scattered dates) (Box 7)
      - Sinclair, Elsie 1980s-1990s (scattered dates) (Box 7)
      - Sinclair, Kathleen 1980s-1990s (scattered dates) (Box 7)
      - Sinclair, Marion ("Sunny") 1980s-1990s (scattered dates) (Box 7)
      - Sinclair, Leni 1983 (Box 7)
      - Sinclair, Penny 1990s (scattered dates) (Box 7)
      - Vaughn, Jack 1995 (Box 7)
      - Vranich, Mick 1994-1995 (Box 7)
  - Artists' Workshop Society/Wayne State Univ. Artists' Society
    - General information, organizational papers and press releases (Box 7)
    - Activities circa November 1964 -June 1967
      (flyers of coming events; most undated except for month)
      - Undated and January-June (year unknown) (Box 7)
      - July-December (year unknown) (Box 7)
    - Art and Artists 1964, 1966 (Box 7)
    - Artists' Worksheets 1965 (Box 7)
    - Bookstores (Box 7)
    - Clippings (Box 7)
    - Correspondence (Box 7)
    - "Detroit Jazz Scene 1965 A Discussion," 1965 (Box 7)
    - Detroit Jazz Society (Box 7)
    - Financial records and Corporation papers (Box 7)
    - Free Poems Among Friends (Box 7)
    - Free Poems Among Friends/Dartmouth and elsewhere (Box 7)
    - Free University of Detroit (Box 7)
    - Jazz Arts Subscription Series (Box 7)
    - Membership and Mailing lists (Box 7)
    - Newsletters (Box 7)
    - Poetics and poetry (Box 7)
    - Programs (Box 7)
    - The Spero (Box 7)
    - Poetry journals (Box 7)
    - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Miscellaneous from Artists' Workshop Society period (Box 7)
  - Artists Workshop Press
    - General (Box 7)
    - Change (Box 7)
    - Guerilla (Box 7)
    - "The National Dopester" (Box 7)
    - Whe're and Work (Box 7)
    - Manuscripts (alphabetical by author)
      - Unsigned, 3 folders (Box 7)
      - Joint authorship (Box 7)
      - A (Box 8)
      - Aldrich, Michael R. (Box 8)
      - B (Box 8)
      - Brett, Peter (Box 8)
      - Brown, Marion (Box 8)
      - C (Box 8)
      - Caplan, Ron (Box 8)
      - Coolidge, Clark (Box 8)
      - Codrescu, Andrei (Box 8)
      - D-E (Box 8)
      - Eichele, Robin (Box 8)
      - English, Ron (Box 8)
      - F (Box 8)
      - Figi, Jerry B. (Box 8)
      - Fraser, Dave (Box 8)
      - G (Box 8)
      - H (Box 8)
      - Harris, Bill (Box 8)
      - Hollo, Anselm (Box 8)
      - Hutton, Bill, 3 folders (Box 8)
      - I-J (Box 8)
      - Jack, S.P. (Box 8)
      - K (Box 8)
      - L (Box 8)
      - Levine, Ronald R. (Box 8)
      - M (Box 8)
      - Maizlish, Mort (Box 8)
      - Malone, Henry (Box 8)
      - McCarthy, Michael (Box 8)
      - Moore, Charles (Box 8)
      - N-O-P-Q (Box 8)
      - Paxton, Tom (Box 8)
      - Perret, Christopher (poetry, and artwork), 5 folders (Box 8)
      - R (Box 8)
      - Rosch, Art (Box 8)
      - S (Box 8)
      - Sandberg, David (Box 8)
      - Semark, Jim, 2 folders (Box 8)
      - Sinclair, David (Box 8)
      - Sinclair, John
        - "Fire Music" and "This is Our Music" (Box 8)
        - General, 8 folders (Box 8)
        - Downbeat: letters, "strictly adlib," "where and when," news-stories (Box 9)
        - Jazz: letters, reviews, articles (Box 9)
      - Sinclair, Leni (Box 9)
      - T-U-V (Box 9)
      - Tysh, George (Box 9)
      - Van Newkirk, Allen (Box 9)
      - W-X-Y-Z (Box 9)
      - Welburn, Ron (Box 9)
      - Younkins, Jerry Allen (Box 9)
    - Publications: Magazines
      - Change/1 (Box 9)
      - Change/2 (Box 9)
      - The Journal April 1965 (Box 9)
      - The Journal, Winter 1966/67 (Box 9)
      - The Journal, Summer 1967 (Box 9)
      - Whe're/1 (Box 9)
      - Work/1 (Box 9)
      - Work/2 (Box 9)
      - Work/3 (Box 9)
      - Work/4 (Box 9)
      - Work/5 (Box 9)
    - Publications: Workshop Books
      - WB/1 The Book of Humors-Jim Semark (Box 9)
      - WB/2 "Sit up Straight"-George Tysh (Box 9)
      - WB/3 This is Our Music-John Sinclair (Box 9)
      - WB/4 Hello-J.D. Whitney (Box 9)
      - WB/5 The Night-Vision Express-Jim Semark (Box 9)
      - WB/6 Free Poems/Among Friends Vol. 1-John Sinclair, ed. (Box 9)
      - WB/7 Write About My Buddies...They're Dead-Jerry Younkins (Box 9)
      - WB/8 Fire Music: a record-John Sinclair (Box 9)
      - WB/9 Runes-Robin Eichele (Box 9)
      - WB/11 Said a meant Ron Caplan (Box 9)
      - WB/12 The Strange Odyssey of Howard Pow!-Bill Hutton (Box 9)
      - WB/13 Free Poems/Among Friends Vol. 2-John and Magdalene Sinclair, eds. (Box 9)
      - WB/15 Hello 2nd edition-J.D. Whitney (Box 9)
      - WB/16 The Sirius Poems-Jerry Younkins (Box 9)
      - WB/17 The Sun-Jim Semark (Box 9)
      - WB/18 Meditations-John Sinclair (Box 9)
      - WB/19 Yup It Is-Tom Mitchell (Box 9)
      - WB/20 alice is in you-ed. rudolph/your sweet all-buzz klingenberger (Box 9)
    - Publications: Other
      - Bloom-John Ka (Box 10)
      - Broadsides no. 1 and no. 2 (Box 10)
      - The Floating Bear no. 33 (Box 10)
      - Friends, living and dead-David Federman (Box 10)
      - The Fugs' songbook (Box 10)
      - in sight-lisa galt (Box 10)
      - Miles Modern Poetry Committee Student Faculty Reading May 6, 1966 (Box 10)
      - The Poem for Warner Stringfellow-John Sinclair (Box 10)
      - Prose contribution to Cuban Revolution-Allen Ginsberg (Box 10)
      - The Protest Papers-ed. by Betty E. Chmaj (Box 10)
        (missing)
      - Revolutionary Letters-Diane Di Prima (Box 10)
      - Sunshine Passed Me By-Shannon M. Miller (Box 10)
      - The Collected Artists Workshop 1965 (Box 10)
      - Ten Wayne Poets 1965 (Box 10)
  - Trans-Love Energies Unlimited
    - Legal and Financial (Box 10)
    - Press releases and flyers-general (Box 10)
    - Graphics (Box 10)
    - Sun Ra (Box 10)
    - Clippings-general and miscellaneous (Box 10)
    - Grande Ballroom, Detroit (Box 10)
    - MC 5
      - Correspondence (Box 10)
      - Press releases (Box 10)
      - Legal, performance contracts and union reports (Box 10)
      - Flyers, handbills, and graphics, 2 folders (Box 10)
      - Clippings, 6 folders (Box 10)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 10)
  - Rainbow Energies, Inc.
    - Agreements and Board of Directors minutes and resolutions (Box 10)
    - Band equipment (Box 10)
    - Corporation records and correspondence (Box 10)
    - Agreements and Board of Directors minutes and resolutions (Box 10)
    - Band equipment (Box 10)
    - Corporation records and correspondence (Box 10)
    - Financial
      - 1972 (Box 10)
      - 1973 (Box 10)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 10)
        (Rainbow Energies and First Zenta Church)
    - Guitar Army/Douglas Books (Box 10)
    - Loans, Taxes, and Miscellaneous (Box 10)
    - Publicity packets August 1972-September 1973, 16 folders (Box 11)
    - First Zenta Church of Ann Arbor
      - Board of Directors minutes and corporation papers (Box 11)
      - Building reports, land contract and house insurance (Box 11)
      - Church of the Tree of Life (Box 11)
      - Financial
        - Undated 1971-1972 (Box 11)
        - 1973 (Box 11)
        - 1974 (Box 11)
      - Loans and taxes (Box 11)
      - Temple fund-rental agreements and accounts (Box 11)
    - Rainbow Trucking Company
      - Correspondence and organizational papers (Box 11)
      - Ann Arbor Sun accounting reports, Vol. 2, no. 8-14 May 5, 1974-September 16, 1974 (Box 11)
      - Brochure and flyers (Box 11)
      - Daily work schedules February-June 1973 (Box 11)
      - Financial
        - 1973, 2 folders (Box 11)
        - 1974 (Box 11)
      - Production and Purchasing reports 1973 (Box 11)
      - Royalties: contracts and reports (Box 11)
      - Inventory, distribution reports and miscellaneous (Box 11)
  - Rainbow Multi-Media Corporation
    - Board of directors minutes and resolutions (Box 11)
    - Bylaws and corporation papers (Box 11)
    - Correspondence
      - Undated 1972 (Box 11)
      - January-June 1973 (Box 11)
      - July-December 1973 (Box 11)
      - 1974 (Box 11)
      - 1975 re. bills; includes bills, 1974-1975 (Box 11)
    - Financial
      - Notes and 1972 (Box 11)
      - 1973, 2 folders (Box 11)
      - 1974, 2 folders (Box 11)
      - Clean up file-creditors' lists (Box 11)
      - Ledger 1972-1973 (Box 12)
      - Ledger (Volume 1)
    - Insurance, legal agreements, loans and taxes (Box 12)
    - Mailing list (Box 12)
    - Payroll books 1973-1974, 2 volumes (Box 12)
    - Payroll lists 1973-1974 (Box 12)
    - Press releases (Box 12)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 12)
    - Ann Arbor Blues Festival 1969-1970 (Box 12)
    - Ann Arbor Blues and Jazz Festival 1972
      - Festival proposals and miscellaneous reports (Box 12)
      - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 12)
      - Financial (Box 12)
      - Ticket information and sales reports (Box 12)
      - Festival LP (Atlantic records), 2 folders (Box 12)
      - Artists contracts (Box 12)
      - Other legal agreements (Box 12)
      - Performer's accommodations and workers' check-in (Box 12)
      - Advertising and official program (Box 12)
      - Press releases and reprinted articles (Box 12)
      - Clippings, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Ann Arbor Blues and Jazz Festival 1973
      - Festival proposals and miscellaneous reports (Box 12)
      - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 12)
      - Financial, 4 folders (Box 12)
      - Recording projects, 2 folders (Box 12)
      - Artists contracts and discography (Box 13)
      - Other legal agreements (Box 13)
      - Advertising (Box 13)
      - Official program and miscellaneous promotional material (Box 13)
      - Press releases and reprinted articles (Box 13)
      - Clippings, 3 folders (Box 13)
    - Ann Arbor Blues and Jazz Festival On Tour May, 1974 (Box 13)
    - Ann Arbor Blues and Jazz Festival In Exile 1974
      - General (Box 13)
      - Correspondence (Box 13)
      - Financial (Box 13)
      - Ticket sales reports (Box 13)
      - Film project (Box 13)
      - Artists contracts (Box 13)
      - Other legal agreements (Box 13)
      - Advertising and promotional material (Box 13)
      - Clippings, 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Energy Sound (Recording) Company
      - General (Box 13)
      - Financial (Box 13)
    - Rainbow Agency
      - Corporation paper, organizational notes and correspondence (Box 13)
      - Advertising schedules, price lists and flyer distribution lists (Box 13)
      - Contracts September-December 1972 (Box 13)
      - Daily sales summaries 1974 (Box 13)
      - Financial
        - Undated, 1973 (Box 13)
        - 1974, 3 folders (Box 13)
        - Ledger 1974 (Box 13)
      - Rainbow advertising (Box 13)
      - Rainbow Press
        - Correspondence, reports and miscellaneous (Box 14)
        - Financial (Box 14)
        - Job flow sheets August-December 1973 and sample production forms (Box 14)
        - Ledger November 1972-December 1973 (Box 14)
      - Rainbow Graphics
        - General (Box 14)
        - Samples
          - Originals-miscellaneous (Box 14)
          - A (Box 14)
          - Ann Arbor Blues and Jazz festivals (Box 14)
          - B (Box 14)
          - Blind Pig (Box 14)
          - C (Box 14)
          - Concert handbills-miscellaneous (Box 14)
          - D (Box 14)
          - E (Box 14)
          - F (Box 14)
          - G-L (Box 14)
          - King Pleasure (Box 14)
          - M (Box 14)
          - N-Q (Box 14)
          - Peoples Ballroom (Box 14)
          - Primo Showbar (Box 14)
          - R (Box 14)
          - Rainbow businesses and Rainbow People's Party (Box 14)
          - Rockets (Box 14)
          - S (Box 14)
          - T-V (Box 14)
          - Up/Uprising (Box 14)
          - W-Z (Box 14)
    - Rainbow Broadcasting Company (WNRZ proposal) (Box 15)
    - Rainbow Management
      - General (Box 15)
      - Ann Arbor and Detroit Federations of Musicians (Box 15)
      - Luther Allison (Box 15)
      - Deliverance (8th Day) (Box 15)
      - Detroit
        - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 15)
        - Press releases and clippings (Box 15)
        - Contracts (performance)
          - 1972 (Box 15)
          - January-June 1973 (Box 15)
          - July-December 1973 (Box 15)
        - Job/Contract information forms May-August 1973 (Box 15)
        - Other legal agreements (Box 15)
        - Financial-general (including "Business Trip") (Box 15)
        - Expense forms
          - August 1972-May 1973 (Box 15)
          - June-July 1973 (Box 15)
          - August-November 1973 (Box 15)
        - Interview transcript June 1973 (Box 15)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 15)
      - Full Tilt Boogie/RMM flood victims benefit (Box 15)
      - Guardian Angel/Lightnin'
        - Correspondence and financial (Box 15)
        - Press releases and clippings (Box 15)
        - Contracts (performance)
          - January-October 1972 Guardian Angel (Box 15)
          - November 1972-July 1973 Lightnin' (Box 15)
          - August 1973-April 1974 Lightnin' (Box 15)
        - Other legal agreements (Box 15)
        - Interview transcript November 1972, band meetings and miscellaneous (Box 15)
      - Mojo Boogie Band and One String Sam (Box 15)
      - Rockets
        - Correspondence and financial (Box 15)
        - Press releases and clippings (Box 15)
        - Contracts
          - September 1972-June 1974 (Box 15)
          - July-November 1974 (Box 15)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 15)
      - Up/Uprising (Up Enterprises/Up Rock and Roll Company)
        - Corporation papers and correspondence (Box 15)
        - Press releases and flyers, 2 folders (Box 15)
      - Up/Uprising (Up Enterprises/Up Rock and Roll Company)
        - Contracts and contract information forms (Box 16)
          - circa 1967-1972 (Box 16)
            (The "UP")
          - March-June 1973 (Uprising) (Box 16)
          - July-December 1973 (Uprising) (Box 16)
        - Financial 1967-1968, 1973 (Box 16)
        - Income Tax returns 1967-1971 (Box 16)
        - Band meeting notes and miscellaneous (Box 16)
    - Rainbow Productions
      - Correspondence (Box 16)
      - Press releases, reports and financial (Box 16)
      - Ann Arbor Video Festival (Box 16)
      - Burning River Productions/Roots and Branches Concerts (Box 16)
      - Fort Wayne Concerts/Starseed Productions
        - Ted Nugent vs. Cactus (Box 16)
        - Leon Russell Show (Box 16)
      - Gold Leaf Productions 1973 (Box 16)
      - Lightnin' session data sheets (Box 16)
      - Morgan Sound (Box 16)
      - Primo Showbar
        - General (Box 16)
        - Contracts
          - July-October 1973 (Box 16)
          - November 1973-March 1974 (Box 16)
      - Rainbow Room, The Shelby
        - Correspondence, agreements and financial (Box 16)
        - Promotional material and clippings (Box 16)
      - Cecil Taylor Unit (Box 16)
      - "Toke Time" programs (Box 16)
      - UAC/Daystar concerts (Box 16)
      - Clippings and miscellaneous (Box 16)
    - Rainbow Records/Rainbow Recording Co. (Box 16)
    - Rainbow Sound Company (Box 16)
  - Rainbow Productions, Inc.
    - Correspondence, agreements, and financial (Box 16)
    - Press releases (Box 16)
    - Tribe/Julian Priester and Marine Intrusion, 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Flyers (Box 16)
    - Graphics (Box 16)